Finding Aid for the Susan Sontag Papers LSC.0612
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 6: Works by Susan Sontag, 1945-2004
  - Sub-series 6.2, 1960-2004; 113 boxes (56.50 lin. ft.) and 12 oversize boxes
    - In America., 1999 December 14. (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Page proofs, second pass with holograph corrections. Folder 3 of 3. Pages 277-388.
    - In America., 1999 November 11. (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Notes and page proofs with manuscript and holograph corrections. Folder 1 of 3. Pages 1-89 and 36 pages.
    - In America., 1999 November 11. (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Notes and page proofs with manuscript and holograph corrections. Folder 2 of 3. Pages 90-241.
    - In America., 1999 November 11. (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Notes and page proofs with manuscript and holograph corrections. Folder 3 of 3. Pages 242-359.
    - In America., 1999 November 11. (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Newspaper, notes, and page proofs with manuscript and holograph corrections. Folder 1 of 3. Pages 3-133 and 14 pages.
    - In America., 1999 November 11. (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Newspaper, notes, and page proofs with manuscript and holograph corrections. Folder 2 of 3. Pages 134-247.
    - In America., 1999 November 11. (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Newspaper, notes, and page proofs with manuscript and holograph corrections. Folder 3 of 3. Pages 248-377.
    - In America., 1999 December 14. (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Page proofs. Folder 1 of 3. Pages 1-110 and 9 pages.
    - In America., 1999 December 14. (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Page proofs. Folder 2 of 3. Pages 111-242.
    - In America., 1999 December 14. (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Page proofs. Folder 3 of 3. Pages 243-388.
    - In America., no date. (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Typescript draft of Catalan translation. Folder 1 of 3. Pages 1-164.
    - In America., no date. (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Typescript draft of Catalan translation. Folder 2 of 3. Pages 165-297.
    - In America., no date. (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Typescript draft of Catalan translation. Folder 3 of 3. Pages 298-420.
    - In America., no date. (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Miscellaneous notes, research material, and manuscript/typescript drafts. ca. 150 pages.
    - In America., 1994 April. (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Faxed drafts from Italy. ca. 22 pages.
    - In America., 1999. (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Larry McMurtry's questions, faxed correspondence. 10 pages.
    - In America., 1992-1999. (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Correspondence with Kasia Gorska. ca. 25 pages.
    - In America., 1999. (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Correspondence with Robert Walsh. 2 pages.
    - In America., 1997-1998. (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Correspondence with John Maxtone-Graham. ca. 40 pages.
    - In America., no date. (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Cover ideas. 11 pages.
    - In America., 2000. (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Publication party invitation and lists. 14 pages and 1 item.
    - In America., 2000. (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Franklin Library Edition. 18 pages.
    - In America., 2000 February 22. (Box 11, Folder 11)
      E-book. 1 page.
    - In America., 1998-1999. (Box 11, Folder 12)
      Statue of Liberty. 20 items.
    - In America., 1993-1998. (Box 11, Folder 13)
      California Historical Society. ca. 38 pages.
    - In America., 1992-1999. (Box 11, Folder 14)
      Various research material. ca. 40 pages.
    - In America., 2000-2001. (Box 11, Folder 15)
      Reactions to the book (including fan letters). 7 pages.
    - In America., 1999 December 17. (Box 11, Folder 16)
      Polish lettering style sheet. 4 pages.
    - In America., 1999. (Box 11, Folder 17)
      Reactions to manuscript. 12 pages.
    - In America., 1998. (Box 11, Folder 18)
      After publication. 2 pages.
    - In America., 1997. (Box 11, Folder 19)
      Jorg Trobitius, German translation. 3 pages.
    - In America., 1998. (Box 11, Folder 20)
      Wylie, Frankfurt copy. 6 pages.
    - In America., 1999-2000. (Box 11, Folder 21)
      Published excerpts (including correspondence from Bonnie Marranca). 4 pages.
    - In America., 2000, 2002, no date. (Box 11, Folder 22)
      Spain and Mexico (translation draft pages and correspondence). 8 pages.
    - In America., 2000. (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Retail information. 9 pages.
    - In America., 2000 March 21. (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Giovannella Zannoni Cineritmo. 2 pages.
    - In America., no date. (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Modjeska archives. Folder 1 of 5. ca. 100 pages.
    - In America., no date. (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Modjeska archives. Folder 2 of 5. ca. 70 pages.
    - In America., 1995 February 14, no date. (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Modjeska archives. Folder 3 of 5. ca. 80 pages.
    - In America., no date. (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Modjeska archives. Folder 4 of 5. ca. 118 pages.
    - In America., no date. (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Modjeska archives. Folder 5 of 5. ca. 66 pages.
    - In America., no date. (Box 12, Folder 8)
      The Old Stock Company School of Acting. ca. 89 pages.
    - In America., no date. (Box 12, Folder 9)
      David Belasco. "My Life's Story." 31 pages.
    - In America., no date. (Box 12, Folder 10)
      Anaheim Research Material. ca. 50 pages.
    - In America., no date. (Box 12, Folder 11)
      Thesis - "The Polish Colony of California 1876-1914". ca. 85 pages.
    - In America., 1952. (Box 12, Folder 12)
      M.A. thesis, University of Southern California. ca. 40 pages.
    - In America., no date. (Box 12, Folder 13)
      Thesis, University of Southern California - "The German Settlement at Anaheim". ca. 40 pages.
    - In America., no date. (Box 12, Folder 14)
      New Modjeska research. ca. 35 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 13, Folder 1)
      "Monkey Business" for Part 1 Ch. 5. ca. 5 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Miscellaneous research material. Folder 1 of 7. ca. 60 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Miscellaneous research material. Folder 2 of 7. ca. 100 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Miscellaneous research material. Folder 3 of 7. ca. 155 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Miscellaneous research material. Folder 4 of 7. ca. 150 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Miscellaneous research material. Folder 5 of 7. ca. 145 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Miscellaneous research material. Folder 6 of 7. ca. 40 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Miscellaneous research material. Folder 7 of 7. ca. 40 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 13, Folder 9)
      Anchor Paper edition. ca. 35 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 13, Folder 10)
      Photocopy of part of Chapter 6. 18 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Typescript drafts of Part I Ch. 5 with holograph corrections. ca. 117 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 14, Folder 2)
      Bound notebook of various Portuguese articles on Sontag. ca. 90 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Holograph notes, chronology, and chapter outlines. 17 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Various typscript drafts with holograph corrections and holograph notes. Folder 1 of 2. ca. 150 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Various typscript drafts with holograph corrections and holograph notes. Folder 2 of 2. ca. 100 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 14, Folder 6)
      Legal pad holograph notes and draft. 23 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 14, Folder 7)
      Typescript draft of Part II Ch.7 and manuscript notes. ca. 70 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1989 Sept - 1990 July. (Box 14, Folder 8)
      Typescript and holograph drafts of Part I Ch.2 with holograph corrections. ca. 60 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 14, Folder 9)
      Typescript page with holograph corrections for program insert. 1 page.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 14, Folder 10)
      Miscellaneous notes and notecards. ca. 24 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 15, Folder 1)
      Early typescript draft of Part I with holograph corrections and chronology of novel. Pages 1-153 with 3 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 15, Folder 2)
      Typescript draft of prologue, Part I Ch.1-3, with holograph corrections. ca. 63 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 15, Folder 3)
      Typescript draft of Part I Ch.4-7 with holograph corrections. 89 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 15, Folder 4)
      Spain. Folder 1 of 3. ca. 200 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 15, Folder 5)
      Spain. Folder 2 of 3. 142 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Spain. Folder 3 of 3. ca. 45 items.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1995. (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Notes on Spanish translation to Marta Pesarrodona. Folder 1 of 2. 105 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1994-1995. (Box 16, Folder 2)
      Notes on Spanish translation to Marta Pesarrodona. Folder 2 of 2. ca. 136 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992-1993. (Box 16, Folder 3)
      Correspondence regarding Spanish translation. Folder 1 of 2. ca. 105 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992-1995. (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Correspondence regarding Spanish translation. Folder 2 of 2. ca. 119 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1989-1995. (Box 16, Folder 5)
      France. ca. 45 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1994-1995. (Box 16, Folder 6)
      Correspondence regarding French translation. ca. 115 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1990-1997. (Box 17, Folder 1)
      France. ca. 84 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992-1995. (Box 17, Folder 2)
      French translation (Bourgois). Folder 1 of 3. ca. 132 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1993-1995. (Box 17, Folder 3)
      French translation (Bourgois). Folder 2 of 3. ca. 155 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992-1993. (Box 17, Folder 4)
      French translation (Bourgois). Folder 3 of 3. ca. 130 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1993. (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Tour. 24 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1993, no date. (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Giuseppe Merlino. 9 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1993. (Box 17, Folder 7)
      Brazilian review. 1 item.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1993-1994. (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Germany. 24 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1991-1992. (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Praise. 18 items.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992. (Box 18, Folder 2)
      Italian interviews. 9 items.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992. (Box 18, Folder 3)
      September Tour. Folder 1 of 2. ca. 120 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992. (Box 18, Folder 4)
      September Tour. Folder 2 of 2. ca. 100 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992. (Box 18, Folder 5)
      Bookseller Lists. ca. 94 pages.
    - In America, no date. (Box 18, Folder 6)
      Flap copy revisions. 1 page.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 18, Folder 7)
      Notes and drafts with holograph corrections. ca. 100 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 18, Folder 8)
      Typescript draft of prologue to Part II Ch.2. Pages 1-170 and 6 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 18, Folder 9)
      "Problems and Queries" and typescript draft of Part II Ch.1-3 with holograph corrections. ca. 100 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1994-1996. (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Italy. ca. 125 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 19, Folder 2)
      Typescript draft of prologue to Part I Ch.3. Pages 1-45 and 2 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 19, Folder 3)
      Notes/Facts "To Add, Maybe." ca. 60 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 19, Folder 4)
      Pageproofs of introductory pages, prologue, and Part I Ch.1. Pages 3- 14 and 8 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 19, Folder 5)
      Typescript drafts of various sections in novel with holograph corrections, and holograph notes. ca. 100 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 19, Folder 6)
      Holograph notes, chronology, and chapter outlines. 100 items.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 19, Folder 7)
      Various typescript drafts of several chapters: "old" or "alternative." ca. 50 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 19, Folder 8)
      Two complete sets of Farrar, Straus & Giroux proofs. Folder 1 of 2. ca. 100 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 19, Folder 9)
      Two complete sets of Farrar, Straus & Giroux page proofs. Folder 2 of 2. ca. 100 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 19, Folder 10)
      Franklin Library special message. 6 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 19, Folder 11)
      Quote checks (holograph notes). 4 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 20, Folder 1)
      Reader's copy. 9 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992. (Box 20, Folder 2)
      Interviews. ca. 70 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 20, Folder 3)
      "Send to." 3 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1985-1995. (Box 20, Folder 4)
      Letters. Folder 1 of 2. ca. 32 items.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1991-1993, 1998. (Box 20, Folder 5)
      Letters. Folder 2 of 2. ca. 47 items.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1995-1998. (Box 20, Folder 6)
      Miniseries. 7 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1993 July 7. (Box 20, Folder 7)
      Denmark. 2 items.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1993. (Box 20, Folder 8)
      Finland. ca. 10 items.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1993-1994. (Box 20, Folder 9)
      Korea. 6 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992-1999. (Box 20, Folder 10)
      Poland. ca. 75 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1994-1999. (Box 20, Folder 11)
      Russia. ca. 20 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992-1993. (Box 20, Folder 12)
      UK: Vintage. 19 items.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992-1995, 1997. (Box 20, Folder 13)
      Audio/movie rights. ca. 30 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 2003-2004. (Box 20, Folder 14)
      Picador (Frances Coady). 11 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992, no date. (Box 20, Folder 15)
      Farrar, Straus & Giroux cover design. 20 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 20, Folder 16)
      Research material on Eusapia Palladino, Neopolitan medium (descendant of Eusapia Pumo). 55 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 20, Folder 17)
      Research material for translators. 45 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1995. (Box 20, Folder 18)
      Spain press and bestseller lists. 12 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 21, Folder 1)
      Typescript draft of French manuscript. Folder 1 of 4. Pages 1-172 and 1 page.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 21, Folder 2)
      Typescript draft of French manuscript. Folder 2 of 4. Pages 173-354.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 21, Folder 3)
      Typescript draft of French manuscript. Folder 3 of 4. Pages 355-537.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 21, Folder 4)
      Typescript draft of French manuscript. Folder 4 of 4. Pages 538-617.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 21, Folder 5)
      Unbound copy. Folder 1 of 2. Pages 1-214.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 21, Folder 6)
      Unbound copy. Folder 2 of 2. Pages 215-419.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 21, Folder 7)
      Paperback corrections. 1 page.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Fact sheets, chronology, etc. 29 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1996. (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Estonia. 3 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1996-1997. (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Greece. 3 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1993 January 20. (Box 22, Folder 4)
      India. 1 page.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1997 November 18. (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Israel. 1 page.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1993-1999. (Box 22, Folder 6)
      Japan. ca. 30 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1994-1995. (Box 22, Folder 7)
      Slovakia. 5 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992-1998, 2000, 2002. (Box 22, Folder 8)
      Fan letters. 20 items.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992, 1999. (Box 22, Folder 9)
      Press. 37 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 22, Folder 10)
      "Draft with alternatives": early draft of Part I with holograph corrections. Pages 1-101 and 8 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 22, Folder 11)
      French translation of prologue and Part I, Chapter 1. Pages 7-34 and 3 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 22, Folder 12)
      Typescript drafts of Part I, Chapter 3 with holograph corrections. ca. 40 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 22, Folder 13)
      Typescript draft of Part II, Chapters 1-3 with holograph corrections. Pages 153-245 and 12 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 23, Folder 1)
      Typescript drafts of Part I, Chapter 6. ca. 110 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 23, Folder 2)
      Final draft. Folder 1 of 3. Pages 1-181 and 3 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 23, Folder 3)
      Final draft. Folder 2 of 3. Pages 182-382.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 23, Folder 4)
      Final draft. Folder 3 of 3. Pages 383-554.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992. (Box 23, Folder 5)
      Franklin Library. ca. 130 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1991-1992. (Box 23, Folder 6)
      Catalog jacket copy. 6 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992. (Box 23, Folder 7)
      New York Publication Party. ca. 40 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 24, Folder 1)
      First draft of prologue with holograph corrections. 3 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 24, Folder 2)
      Early draft of prologue, Part I, Chapters 1, 2, and some of 4 with holograph corrections. ca. 70 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 24, Folder 5)
      Typescript draft of Dutch translation with holograph corrections. Folder 1 of 4. Pages 1-149.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 24, Folder 6)
      Typescript draft of Dutch translation with holograph corrections. Folder 2 of 4. Pages 150-292.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 24, Folder 7)
      Typescript draft of Dutch translation with holograph corrections. Folder 3 of 4. Pages 293-468.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 24, Folder 8)
      Typescript draft of Dutch translation with holograph corrections. Folder 4 of 4. Pages 469-612.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1993. (Box 25, Folder 1)
      Correspondence with Dutch translator. Folder 1 of 2. ca. 185 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1993. (Box 25, Folder 2)
      Correspondence with Dutch translator. Folder 2 of 2. ca. 190 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992-1993. (Box 25, Folder 3)
      Correspondence with Portugese translator. Folder 1 of 2. ca. 170 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1993. (Box 25, Folder 4)
      Correspondence with Portugese translator (Brazil). Folder 2 of 2. ca. 180 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 25, Folder 5)
      Invitation to publicaton party. 2 items.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 25, Folder 6)
      Handwritten incomplete drafts of various chapters. ca. 20 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 25, Folder 7)
      "Must Use": typescript notes. 2 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 25, Folder 8)
      Holograph and typescript draft of various pages. ca. 75 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Research articles. Folder 1 of 3. ca. 200 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 26, Folder 2)
      Research articles. Folder 2 of 3. ca. 140 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 26, Folder 3)
      Research articles. Folder 3 of 3. ca. 200 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 26, Folder 4)
      Publisher's typescript draft. Folder 1 of 3. Pages 1-142.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 26, Folder 5)
      Publisher's typescript draft. Folder 2 of 3. Pages 143-274.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 26, Folder 6)
      Publisher's typescript draft. Folder 3 of 3. Pages 275-419.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992. (Box 27, Folder 1)
      Various typescript and holograph notes. ca. 200 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 27, Folder 2)
      Publisher's typescript draft. Folder 1 of 2. Pages 15-206.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 27, Folder 3)
      Publisher's typescript draft. Folder 2 of 2. Pages 207-419.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 27, Folder 4)
      Typescript draft of Part I, Chapters 1-7. Pages 10-143.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 27, Folder 5)
      Holograph research notes. ca. 150 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 27, Folder 6)
      Notebooks. 2 items. See also Journals series
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1984-1991. (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Miscellaneous magazine clippings and other material. ca. 25 items.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 28, Folder 2)
      Typescript draft with Farrar, Straus & Giroux proofreader's marks. Folder 1 of 3. Pages 1-168.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 28, Folder 3)
      Typescript draft with Farrar, Straus & Giroux proofreader's marks. Folder 2 of 3. Pages 169-361.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 28, Folder 4)
      Typescript draft with Farrar, Straus & Giroux proofreader's marks. Folder 3 of 3. Pages 362-554.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1993. (Box 28, Folder 5)
      Final draft with photocopies of replacement pages. Folder 1 of 3. Pages 1-116.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1993. (Box 28, Folder 6)
      Final draft with photocopies of replacement pages. Folder 2 of 3. Pages 117-252.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1993. (Box 28, Folder 7)
      Final draft with photocopies of replacement pages. Folder 3 of 3. Pages 253-419.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Typescript draft: "Current." Folder 1 of 3. Pages 1-183.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 29, Folder 2)
      Typescript draft: "Current." Folder 2 of 3. Pages 184-347.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., no date. (Box 29, Folder 3)
      Typescript draft: "Current." Folder 3 of 3. Pages 348-554.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1994-1995. (Box 29, Folder 4)
      Italy clippings. ca. 9 items.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1995. (Box 29, Folder 5)
      Sweden reviews. ca. 60 items.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992-1994. (Box 29, Folder 6)
      Hungary. ca. 8 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992-1994. (Box 29, Folder 7)
      Norway. ca. 30 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1984. (Box 29, Folder 8)
      Piero Guccione: 1984 text. 11 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992-1994. (Box 29, Folder 9)
      Sweden. ca. 80 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1993. (Box 30, Folder 1)
      German tour. ca. 150 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992-1993. (Box 30, Folder 2)
      German translation (Hanser). Folder 1 of 2. ca. 110 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992-1993. (Box 30, Folder 3)
      German translation (Hanser). Folder 2 of 2. ca. 100 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992-1994. (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Italian translation (Mondadori). ca. 120 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992-1994. (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Holland. ca. 35 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1993. (Box 30, Folder 6)
      Brigitte (Hanser). ca. 19 pages.
    - Volcano Lover (The)., 1992-1993. (Box 30, Folder 7)
      German press. ca. 100 pages and 1 item. Includes cassette tape
      BOX CONTAINS AUDIO AND AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audio and audiovisual materials in this collection will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.